Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibition files, 1944-2009; 1983-2009; Series 11
  - Dan Flavin: Press Release, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Gladys Nelson Smith: Original Press Release, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Gladys Nelson Smith: Background, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Baron Philippe de Rothschild, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mouton Rothschild - Background, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mouton 2 page letter + original, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - [Mouton Rothschild: Labels, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Mouton Rothschild Press Release, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Print/Non-print coverage, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Labels by Year, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Mouton Rothschild: John Huston, 1982; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Andy Warhol, 1975; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Robert Motherwell, 1974; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Pablo Picasso, 1973; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Marc Chagall, 1970; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Joan Miro, 1969; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Mouton Rothschild: de Lippold, 1959; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Salvador Dali, 1958; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Georges Braque, 1955; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Mouton Rothschild: Jean Carlu, 1924; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Pennsylvania Lanndscape: press releases, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Pennsylvania Landscape: background, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Clipping Copies: Trustees, 1984; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - [Clipping Copies: Craig Unger, 1984; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Original Clippings: One Of A Kind: Monotypes From The Collection, 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Joshua Johnston Acquisition press clippings, originals, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Moulin Rouge Gala: Clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - 1983 Clippings: artists' coalition, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - 1983 Clipping Copies: Corcoran References, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - 1983 Clipping Copies: Music Programs, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - 1983 Clippings: Staff, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - 1983 Clipping Copies: Fundraising, Funding, Grants, Gifts, 1984; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: Fundraising, Funding, Grants, Gifts, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: Corcoran References, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: School, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: Affordable Art Auction, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: Special Events, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: Musical Events, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - 1984 Clipping Copies: The Corcoran Collection, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - 1984 Archives Show, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - 1984 Recent Acquisitions, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - 1985 Corcoran Referencecs, Clippings, Copies, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - 1985 Corcoran Staff, Clippings, Copies, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Ned Rifkin: Clippings (copies), Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Ned Rifkin: Clippings (originals), Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Prints by Whistler, 1982 July 12 - September 26; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - August Sander: Photogrraphs of an Epoch, 1904-1959; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Sam Gilliam, 1983 March 24 - May 22; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Still Life: Photographs From The Collection of The Museum of Art, 1982 July 10 - August 29; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - [Artists Architects Collaboration], Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Counterparts, 1983 March 5 - May 8; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Christenberry: Photos and slides, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - John Singer Sargent - drawings, etc. from the collection, 1983 June 14 - September 4; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Wegman's World, 1983 July 9 - August 28; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Washington Watercolors, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - A Still Life, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Nicholas Nixon, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Rockne Krebs, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - The Grand Tour, 1983 September 24 - November 13; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - [Daumier], Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Malcolm Morley, 1983 September 10 - November 6; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Emmet Gowin, 1983 September 17 November 13; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - The Grand Tour, 1983 September 24 - November 13; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Arthur B. Carles Xeroxed Clippings, 1983 September 10 - November 11; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Constance Larrabee, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - 1983 Clippings One of a Kind: Monotype from the Collection, Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Clippings: Corcoran Biennial, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Joshua Joohnston Acquisition Clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Moulin Rouge Galla press clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Bequests (Archives) press clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Artists' Coalition: Press Clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - 1983 Press Clippings School, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - 1983 Clippings - Corcoran References, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - 1983 Press Clippings: Music Programs, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - 1983 Press Clippings: Recent Acquisitions, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - 1983 Press Clippings: Botwinick, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - 1983 Press Clippings: Staff, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - 1983 Clippings: Funding, Fundraising, Gifts, Grants, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - La Vie Moderne Clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Black Folk Art Clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Alan Sonfist clippings, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - [Chinese Traditional Painting: Five Midern Masters exhibit], Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - 1984 Clippings: Affordable Art Auction, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - 1984 Clippings: Botwinick, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - 1984 Clippings: Staff, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - 1984 Clippings: Trustees, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - 1984 Clippings: School, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - 1984 Clippings: Musical Events, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - 1984 Press Clippings: Funding, Fundraising, Gifts, Grants, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - 1984 Clippings: Special Events, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - 1984 Clippings: Shops, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - 1984 Clippings: Archives Shows, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - 1984 Clippings: Recent Acquisitions, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - 1984 Clippings: Education Program, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - 1984 Clippings: Advertising, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - 1984 Clippings: The Corcoran Collection, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - 1984 Clippings: Corcoran References, Circa 1983; Series 11 (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - FY 89 Japanese Photography - Release, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - FY 89 Japanese Photography Checklist, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - FY 89 Japanese Photography Brochures, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - FY 89 Japanese Photography - Correspondence, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - FY 89 Japanese Photography - Press Clips, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - FY 89 Japanese Photography - Background, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - Press Release, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - Checklist, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - B/W Glossies Avail, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - Philly Release, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - Press Clips, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - Correspondence, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - FY 89 Robert Adams - Letters to PhotoEd., 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - FY 88 Transco Watercolors - Labels, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - FY 88 Transco Watercolors - Press Release, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - FY 88 Transco Watercolors - Background, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - FY 88 Transco Watercolors - Correspondence, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - FY 88 Transco Watercolors - Checklist, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - FY 88 Charles Simonds Background, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - FY 88 Charles Simonds - Release, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - FY 88 Charles Simonds - Correspondence, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - FY 88 Charles Simonds - Catalogues, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - FY 88 Charles Simonds - Labels, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - FY 88 Soviet Artists - History, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - FY 88 Soviet Artists - Press Release, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - FY 88 Soviet Artists - Correspondence, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - FY 88 Soviet Artists - Press Preview, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - FY 88 Soviet Artists - Press Kit, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Press Release, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Lecture Release, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Cartoonist Bios, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Background, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Correspondence, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Press Preview, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Brochures/Cataloguees, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - FY 88 New Yorker - Press Kit, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Hispanic Originals, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Hispanic Checklist, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Master Background File, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Hispanic Bios., 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - contacts in Hispanic community, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Press Release, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Correspondence, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Transparancies, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - B/W Available, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Slides, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Press Kit, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show - Advisory Committee, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - FY '88 Hispanic Show Clips, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - FY '88 Encard Letters, Hispanic Show, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - [Joan Mitchell Bio.], 1987; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Joan Mitchell - Checklist, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Joan Mitchell - Press Preview, 1988; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Joan Mitchell - Original Clippings, 1974; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Joan Mitchell - Correspondence, 1987; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Joan Mitchell - Press Kit/Catalogues, 1987; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Slides Glossies Available Lichtenstein FY 89, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Joan Mitchell - Lichenstein - MOMA Background info FY 89, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Lichenstein FY 89 Correspondence, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - FY 89 Lichtenstein Press Release, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Holly Wright - Background Inifo. FY 89, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - FY 89 Holly Wright - Labels, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - FY 89 Holly Wright - Correspondence, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - FY 89 Holly Wrighht - press release, 1989; Series 11 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Wyeth Articles, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Wyeths - Slides + Glossies, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Wyeth Art: An American Vision, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Wyeth Clippings 1987, Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Wyeth Black/White Photos, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Wyeth Clippings and Regular Sized already xeroxed, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Wyeth Clippings already copied, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Hispanic BW Glossies and Slides Transparencies, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Hispanic Addendum, 1987-1988; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Hispanic Clippings that have already been xeroxed, 1987; Series 11 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - [Odyssey Itinerary], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Odyssey Prints, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Nat. Geo. - Black and White Avail., Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Nat. Geo. - Slides and Trans Avail., Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Geo. Tour - Letter to Museums - PR (Empty), Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Geo. Tour Museum Addresses, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - New Press Release (Empty), Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - [B, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Travel Writers, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Transparencies (Empty), Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - [150 Years of Photography], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Geo - Press Preview, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - National Geo. Press Work, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Odyssey Slides, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - [Sesquicentennial of Photography PR], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - [Odyssey Adendum and Bobbi Faul], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Sacre, Edmond Beguines of Ghent, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Schoedsack, Ernest Siam (Thailand), Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Wiele and Klein India Religious Penances, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Wulsin, Frederick, Choni, China Kitchen, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Minshall, Merlin Graf Zeppelin, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Ponting, Herbert B. Day Member of Scott Expedition, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Reed, Roland Enemy Wind, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Rock, Joseph Choni, China Lama Caretaker, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Almasy, Paul Madagascar, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Chase, Lynwood Star-Nosed Mole, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Edgerton, Harold Bullet Through Balloons, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Enami, Tamotsu Japanese Junks, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Marden, Luis Traveling Barber, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert Alexander Graham Bell w/ Grandchild, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Lehnert Landrock Algeria, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Locke, Justin Newspaper Stand, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - [Odyssey], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Thomasson-Grant Release, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - National Geographic Photography, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Tickertron Release, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Master Set of Slides Extras (empty), Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Slides - Second Page, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Odyssey: Master Set of Slides, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Slides - First Page, Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - [Odyssey Negatives], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - [Odyssey Brochure], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - [Odyssey Negatives], Circa 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - A New World Correspondence, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - New World: Gallery Guide, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - A New World: Checklist of Exhib, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - New World: Photo Orders, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - New World: Taxi Receipts, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - New World: Color Slides, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - A New World: United Technologies, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - A New World: Uncrating - Media Arrangement, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - New World: Original Releases, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - New World: Boston: Checklist, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - New World: Boston: Photo Checklist, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - New World: Whistler's Mother, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - New World: Boston: Basic Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - A New World: Ticketing Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Ticketing Release 1/27/84, 1984 January 27; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Basic Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - New World Basic Extended Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - New World: Expanded Basic Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - New World; Checklist, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - A New World: Fact Sheet, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - New World: Fact Sheet, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Little Known Facts: New World, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - New World: Little Known Facts, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Photos Available List: New World, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - New World: Shop Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - New World: Whistler's Mother Backgrounder, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Whistler's Mother Release Uncrating: New World, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - New World: UTC's Art Statement, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - New World Shop Slides, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - New World Photos: Bingham, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - New World Photos: F. Church, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - New World Photos: T. Cole, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Copley: Paul Revere New World Photos, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - New World Photos Copley: Watson Shark, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - New World Photos Durand: Kindred Spirits, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - New World Photos Eakins: A. Van Buren, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - New World Photos Eakins: Gross Clinic, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Homer, Eight Bells, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Homer, Snap the Whip, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Peale, Rembrandt, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Sargent, Dr. Pozzi, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Sargent, Madame X, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Tait, A Tight Fix, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Whistler, Mother, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Michael Evans: Portraits of Power (Background), Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - [People and Power], Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - People Power: Exh. Checklist, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - People Power: B, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - People Power: Additional pg for cat -- to index of names, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Robert Henri: Painter Background, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Henri: Painter - Press Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Henri, Henri's Circle: Special Programs, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Henri: "Robert Henri, Himself" Program Press Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Henri: Originals, Copy negs, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Henri: Painter Salome b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Henri: Painter: Spanish Dancer b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Henri: Painter; Hughie the poet b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Henri: Painter: George Luks b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Henri: Painter Viv in blue stripe b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Henri: Painter: Laundress b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Henri: Painter: John Sloan b/w, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Henri's Circle: Checklist of Exhibit, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Dunlap: Press Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Dunlap: Brochures, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - [William Dunlap], Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Dunlap B, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Dunlap B, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Dunlap B, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Dunlap B, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Washington Show Press Release, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Washington Show: June Programs, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Washington Show: Mayor's Proclamation, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Washington Show: Exhibition Checklist, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - The Washington Show: Original b/ws copy negs, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - (B/W) Antone, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - (B/W) Boghassian, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - (B/W) Braunstein, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - (B/W) Brennan, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - (B/W) Garripoli, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - (B/W) Goldberg, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - (B/W) Kuter, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - (B/W) Love, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - (B/W) Martin, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - (B/W) Miller, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - (B/W) Monteith, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - (B/W) Nalls, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - (B/W) Richardson, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - (B/W) Woodward, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - (B/W) Yamaguchi, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - The Washington Show, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Diane Arbus: Magazine Work Background, Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - [Diane Arbus: Magazine Work], Circa 1984; Series 11 (Box 31, Folder 48)